Inventory of the Gerald Fried papers, 1941-2014
University of Wyoming. American Heritage Center.
Gerald Fried papers
1941-2014
Fried, Gerald
02883
64.16 cubic ft. (122) + 1.82 MB
University of Wyoming. American Heritage Center.
Gerald Fried was a music composer, musician, author and arranger for television and motion pictures. Collection contains music scores, movie and television production notes, audio recordings, and photographs regarding his career.
Biography of Gerald Fried
Gerald Fried (b. 1928) was a music composer, musician, author and arranger for television and motion pictures. Educated at Juilliard, he performed in the Dallas Symphony, the New York Little Orchestra and the Pittsburgh Symphony before his career as a freelance composer for television and movies. He wrote musical scores for "Dynasty," "Roots," "Sixth Sense," "Survivor," "Man Eater," "Star Trek," "Mannix," "Mission Impossible" "Gilligan's Island," "Ben Casey" and "The Man from U.N.C.L.E." His musical scores for films include "The Killing," "Paths of Glory," "Cold Wind in August," "The Cabinet of Dr. Caligari," "Dino," "Timbuktu," "Machine Gun Kelly," and many others.
Scope and Content
Collection contains motion picture scores, television production scores, audio recordings of motion picture music composed and /or arranged by Gerald Fried, and photographs. Motion picture titles included in the collection are "Bayou," "Caligari," "Dino," "Cold Wind in August," "Machine Gun Kelly," "Timbuktu," "The Restless Breed," "Terror in a Texas Town," and "The Young Lions". Television titles include "Ben Casey," "Gunsmoke," "Jericho," "The Man from U.N.C.L.E.," and many others.
Access Restrictions
There are no access restrictions on the materials for research purposes, and the collection is open to the public.
Related Materials
There are no known other archival collections created by Gerald Fried at the date of processing.
Acquisition Information
This material was received from Gerald Fried from 1990-2017.
Access Terms
Composition (Music); Arrangers (Musicians) -- United States -- 20th century.; Composers -- United States -- 20th century.; Television music.; Motion picture music.; Film composers.; Musical sketches.
Arts, Humanities, and Social Sciences; Music; Performing Arts
Container List
- Series I. Personal Files
  - Appraisal of Gerald Fried's Music Manuscripts, August 1, 1968, undated (Box 1)
  - Award, "Official Title of Geezer", February 13, 1998 (Box 1)
  - Audio
    - Cassette: G.F. at Klon, undated (Box 100)
    - Cassette: Gerald Fried Interviews (Box 100)
    - Cassettes: Gerald Fried on WNYC (3 tapes), November 1994 (Box 100)
    - Cassettes: Gerald Fried on "Spinning On Air" with David Garland WNYC-FM (4 tapes), 1993-1994 (Box 100)
    - CD: Gerald Fried Demo #1, undated (Digital, ahcdm_02883_116)
    - CDs: Fried Samplers, undated (Digital, ahcdm_02883_305-307)
    - CDs: Gerald Fried Interviews, 1993-1994 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_154-160)
    - CDs: Gerald Fried - Cassette Compilations #1-2, TV Music, Sampler, undated (Digital, ahcdm_02883_444-449)
    - CDs: Gerry Fried Tapes - Folk Songs, Dan's Bar-Mitzvah, Jon's Bar-Mitzvah, Josh's Bar-Mitzvah, Family Tapes #1-7, undated (Digital, ahcdm_02883_211-221)
    - DAT Cassettes: Gerald Fried #1-6, undated (Digital, ahcdm_02883_409-414)
    - DAT cassettes: Screen Archives - Gerald Fried, undated (Digital, ahcdm_02883_394-401, 419)
  - Juilliard School of Music Transcript, February 2nd, 1945 (Box 1)
  - Photographs and Prints
    - Family Photographs, 1941-2010, undated (Box 1)
    - Gerry Fried, undated (Digital, ahcdm_02883_302-304)
    - Miscellaneous Photographs, 1947-2009, undated (Box 1)
    - Miscellaneous Prints, 1949-2014, undated (Box 1)
    - Miscellaneous Negatives, undated (Box 110)
    - Miscellaneous Prints, 1950-2014, undated (Box 1)
    - Negative: Photo of Gerald Fried, undated (Box 110)
    - Negative: Photo of Gerald Fried and Friends, undated (Box 110)
    - Negative: Photo of Gerald Fried Taken by Stanley Kubrick, undated (Box 110)
    - Raft Trip 2011 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_300)
    - Anne Staveley Portrait Photography, undated (Digital, ahcdm_02883_301)
  - Stanley Kubrick Correspondence, 1991 (Box 1)
- Series II. Professional Files
  - Incomplete Score, untitled, undated (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1962-1988, undated (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous Cue Sheets, 1 of 2, 1951-1998 (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous Cue Sheets, 2 of 2, 1951-1998 (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous Printed Material & Newspaper Clippings, 1 of 2, 1953-2009 (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous Printed Material & Newspaper Clippings, 2 of 2, 1953-2009 (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous Programs & Clippings, 1953-2014, undated (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous Research Material & Programs, 1952-2010, undated (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous Song Lists, 1958-2009, undated (Box 2)
- Series III. Project Files
  - Sub-series 1. Albums
    - The Mystic Warrior
      - Album Preparation Material, 1984, undated (Box 3)
      - Album Preparation Material, 1984-1992, undated (Box 3)
      - Cassette: Gerald Fried - "The Mystic Warrior", 1984 (Box 46)
      - Cassettes: Masters (3 tapes), 1984 (Box 100)
      - CD, 1977 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_040)
      - DAT cassettes, 1984 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_389-393, 415)
      - Magnetic Tape, May, 1993 (Box 103)
    - Orienta
      - Album Scores, undated (Box 3)
      - Album Scores, undated (Box 3)
      - Cassette, 1959 (Box 100)
    - Vampire Circus Featuring The Return of Dracula: The Essential Vampire Theme Collection
      - Cassette Tape: Vampire Compilation, CD Proof, 1972 (Box 98)
  - Sub-series 2. Concert Works
    - The Chess Game, Musical Piece Based on Lewis Carroll's Through the Looking Glass
      - CD, undated (Digital, ahcdm_02883_246)
      - CD: "The Chess Game" in Santa Fe, 2009 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_111)
      - Score & Notes, 2006 (Box 3)
    - Divertimento for Oboe, and Bassoon
      - Score, September, 1956 (Box 3)
    - Helen of Troy
      - Score, undated (Box 3)
    - The Mystic Warrior
      - Brass Instruments Parts, undated (Box 4)
      - Full Score, 2002 (Box 4)
      - Indian Lyrics & Cue Sheets, 1983-1986, undated (Box 4)
      - Lead Sheets, Instrumental, undated (Box 4)
      - Los Alamos Concert,Press Material, 2003 (Box 4)
      - Master Vocal Score, 2002 (Box 5)
      - Rehearsal Score (Piano) & Chorus (No Piano), Master, undated (Box 5)
      - Score, 2002 (Box 4)
      - Score & Parts, Master Copy, 1 of 2, undated (Box 4)
      - Score & Parts, Master Copy, 2 of 2, undated (Box 4)
      - Score Used for Roger Wagner Tour, 1984 (Box 4)
      - Viola, Cello, Bass Parts, undated (Box 5)
      - Violin I Parts, undated (Box 5)
      - Violin II Parts, undated (Box 5)
      - Woodwinds Parts, undated (Box 5)
    - Omnia Ad Dei Gloriam, or Les the Least Straightens the Lord
      - Alto Sax Parts (Bound), 1964 (Box 5)
      - Baritone Sax Parts (Bound), 1964 (Box 5)
      - Black & White Contact Print Sheets of Los Angeles Performance, May, 1966 (Box 5)
      - Black & White Prints of Los Angeles Performance, May, 1966 (Box 5)
      - Cassette, 1966 (Box 100)
      - CDs: Photos, Masters, Deputy Seraph and Alternative Version, 1966 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_049-052)
      - Clippings, 1966-2008-, undated (Box 105)
      - Complete Conductor's Orchestral Score, 1964 (Box 8)
      - Correspondence, 1964-1966, undated (Box 105)
      - Correspondence, Reviews, Programs and Photographs from the New york Musical Theatre Festival, 2013 (Box 5)
      - Drum Set Parts (Bound), 1964 (Box 5)
      - Libretto, 1964 (Box 5)
      - Los Angeles Performance, Reviews and Programs, May, 1966 (Box 5)
      - Negatives: UCLA, Royce Hall Performance, May, 1966 (Box 110)
      - Part I, Piano Sheets, undated (Box 5)
      - Percussion Parts (Bound), 1964 (Box 5)
      - Photographs (Black & White), 1964-1966, undated (Box 105)
      - Program and Script, 1964-1966 (Box 5)
      - Score (Bound), 1951-1964 (Box 8)
      - Score, Master (Bound), 1964 (Box 107)
      - Score (Bound), 1964 (Box 5)
      - Score (Bound), 1964 (Box 5)
      - Score (Bound), 1964 (Box 5)
      - Score (Bound), 1964 (Box 5)
      - Score (Bound), 1964 (Box 5)
      - Score with Dividers (Bound), 1964 (Box 5)
      - Screen Treatment, 1964 (Box 5)
      - Scripts, 1964 (Box 105)
      - String Bass Parts (Bound), 1964 (Box 5)
      - Trombone Parts (Bound), 1964 (Box 5)
      - Trumpet Parts (Bound), 1964 (Box 5)
      - Vocal Score, Conductor Copy (Bound), 1964 (Box 5)
    - Quartet for Oboe, Violin, Viola, and Cello
      - Score, undated (Box 9)
    - Rock of Angels
      - Cassette: Demo, undated (Box 100)
      - Full Score Used as Master, 1996 (Box 9)
      - Score, Master Corrections (Bound), 1996 (Box 10)
      - Screenplay, 1996 (Box 10)
      - Vocal Score (Bound), 1996 (Box 10)
    - Roots Symphonic Suite
      - Cassette: "Roots" (Main Theme, UCLA Excerpts, Live Performance, Suite, Beach Cities), 1977 (Box 99-100)
      - CD, 1977 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_244)
      - Concert Score, 1995 (Box 7)
      - Concert Score, undated (Box 11)
      - Full Score, 1 of 2, undated (Box 7)
      - Full Score, 2 of 2, undated (Box 7)
      - Programs and Other Related Material, 1995-1996 (Box 108)
      - Score 1 of 2, undated (Box 6)
      - Score 2 of 2, undated (Box 6)
      - Score, Bass Parts, Stands 1 & 2, undated (Box 7)
      - Score, Bass Trombone, Trombone and Tuba Parts, undated (Box 7)
      - Score, Bassoon 1, 2 and Clarinet 1,2 Parts, undated (Box 7)
      - Score,"BBI Concert Band Series", Selections from "Roots", 1977 (Box 6)
      - Score, Cello Parts, Stands 1 & 2, undated (Box 7)
      - Score, Cello Parts, Stands 3 & 4, undated (Box 7)
      - Score, Flutes, 1,2 & Oboes, 1,2 Parts, undated (Box 7)
      - Score, "Gathering Mob", undated (Box 6)
      - Score, Harmonica, Banjo and Guitar Parts, undated (Box 108)
      - Score, Horns 1,2,3, and 4 Parts, undated (Box 108)
      - Score, "Kizzy and chicken George", undated (Box 6)
      - Score, "Knoxville Riots", undated (Box 6)
      - Score, "Memories", undated (Box 6)
      - Score, "New Home", undated (Box 6)
      - Score, Percussions, 1,2,3,4 and 5 Parts, undated (Box 108)
      - Score, "Surrender/Freedom", undated (Box 6)
      - Score, Trumpets 1,2, and 3 Parts, undated (Box 108)
      - Score, Violas, 1 and 2 Parts, undated (Box 108)
      - Score, Violas, Stands 3 and 4, undated (Box 108)
      - Score, Violin I, Stands 1,2, and 3, undated (Box 108)
      - Score, Violin I, Stands 4,5,and 6, undated (Box 108)
      - Score, Violin II, Stands 1,2, and 3, undated (Box 108)
      - Score, Violin II, Stands 4 and 5, undated (Box 108)
      - Score, "Walking to Manhood", undated (Box 6)
      - "Supersound Series for Yound Bands", Selections, 1977 (Box 6)
      - Symphonic Suite (Bound), 1995 (Box 6)
    - Symphony #2, Unfinished
      - Score, undated (Box 11)
    - Three Songs from Silver Pennies
      - Score, 1954 (Box 11)
    - Time Travel for Oboe, and Orchestra
      - CD, undated (Digital, ahcdm_02883_245)
      - Full Score, undated (Box 11)
      - Notes, Reviews and Program, 1997, undated (Box 12)
      - Score and Parts, Performance Ready, undated (Box 12)
      - Score, Bass Sheets, Performance Ready, undated (Box 12)
      - Score, Cello Sheets, Performance Ready, undated (Box 12)
      - Score, Harp, Percussion, Piano and Timpani Sheets, Perfomance Ready, undated (Box 12)
      - Score, Horns, Trombones, Trumpets and Tuba Sheets, Performance Ready, undated (Box 12)
      - Score, Viola Sheets, Performance Ready, undated (Box 12)
      - Score, Violin I Sheets, Performance Ready, undated (Box 12)
      - Score, Violin II Sheets, Performance Ready, undated (Box 12)
    - The Treasure, an Opera in One Cat and Three Scenes
      - Reel-to-Reel, 1987 (Box 103)
      - Score and Program, 1953 (Box 11)
    - Two Themes for Four Flutes
      - Score, November 4, 1955 (Box 11)
  - Sub-series 3. Documentaries
    - Australia's Animal Mysteries
      - CDs and Reel-to-Reels: Master with Slates; Isolated, Sequenced, undated (Box 103 and Digital, ahcdm_02883_201-202)
      - Score, 1 of 2, 1982 (Box 13)
      - Score, 2 of 2, 1982 (Box 13)
    - Birds Do It, Bees Do It
      - CD: Final Master, 1974 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_176)
      - Score, 1 of 2, undated (Box 14)
      - Score, 2 of 2, undated (Box 14)
    - California
      - Score, undated (Box 14)
    - Dear Mr. Gable
      - CDs: Masters and Slates, undated (Digital, ahcdm_02883_042-044)
      - Score, Conductor Sheets, undated (Box 15)
      - Conductor Sheets, January 28, 1968-February 1st, 1968 (Box 16)
    - The Enchanted Years
      - Reel-to-Reel and CDs, 1971 (Box 102 and Digital, ahcdm_02883_144-146)
      - Score, undated (Box 18)
    - Gauguin in Tahiti
      - Cassette, undated (Box 100)
      - CD and Reel-to-Reels: Reels 1-3, 1967 (Box 98 and Digital, ahcdm_02883_033)
      - DAT Cassettes, 1980 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_415-418)
      - Score, undated (Box 18)
    - Hong Kong: A Family Portrait
      - CD and Reel-to-Reel: Sequenced Master, undated (Box 103 and Digital, ahcdm_02883_205-206)
      - Score, undated (Box 18)
    - Once Before I Die
      - Reel-to-Reel, 1966 (Box 101)
      - Score, 1970 (Box 17)
    - Specials for United Artists: December 7th - the Day of Infamy
      - CD: Master, 1963 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_227)
      - Score, undated (Box 16)
    - Specials for United Artists: Ten Seconds That Shook the World
      - Score, undated (Box 17)
    - Specials for United Artists: Winged World
      - Score, undated (Box 17)
    - Story of a Rodeo Cowboy
      - CD, 1963 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_180)
      - CD: Edited Version, 2011 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_299)
    - World of Discovery: The Secret Life of 118 Green Street
      - Cassette Tapes, CD and Reel-to-Reels: 1-2 and Demo, 1990 (Box 98 and Digital, ahcdm_02883_034)
      - Score, undate (Box 19)
  - Sub-series 4. Miscellaneous
    - 4 English Songs Dedicated to Dame Margot Fonteyn
      - Score & Parts, 1953-1954 (Box 3)
    - Bio-Satellite
      - Scores, 1965 (Box 20)
    - C.B.S Billboards
      - Scores, 1964, undated (Box 20)
    - Cities (Charles Eames)
      - CD and Reel-to-Reel: Charles Eames "Image of a City", 1969 (Box 102 and Digital, ahcdm_02883_143)
      - Score, undated (Box 20)
    - Electra(Play)
      - Score and Notes, 1977 (Box 20)
    - Everyman
      - Miscellaneous Scores, undated (Box 20)
    - Garbage Man
      - Score, undated (Box 21)
    - Getting There First
      - CD and 2 Reel-to-Reels: Master with Slates, Revised Sequence, undated (Box 103 and Digital, ahcdm_02883_199-200)
      - Score, 1 of 2, undated (Box 21)
      - Score, 2 of 2, undated (Box 21)
    - The Gift of Time
      - Cassette: Soundtrack, undated (Box 99)
      - Cassettes: Master and Vocal, undated (Box 100)
      - Reel-to-Reel: "Gift of Time", undated (Box 98)
      - Score and Parts, undated (Box 22)
    - Italic Sketches
      - 4 Reel-to-Reels, undated (Box 104)
      - Scores, undated (Box 22)
    - National Parks
      - Cassette: One Channel Missing, undated (Box 100)
      - Score, undated (Box 22)
    - Old McDonald, undated
      - Cassette, undated (Box 100)
    - Outlander, undated
      - 2 Cassettes, undated (Box 100)
    - Princess in Tower, undated
      - CD, undated (Digital, ahcdm_02883_337)
    - Psychling
      - Score, undated (Box 22)
    - To the Moon and Beyond, 1964 NY World's Fair
      - CD, 1964 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_177)
      - CD: Commercial Demos, undated (Digital, ahcdm_02883_184)
      - Score, 1964 (Box 24)
    - Various and Mixed Titles
      - Betamax Tape: Unidentified, undated (Box 100)
      - Cassette: 12 Tone Unknown, undated (Box 99)
      - Cassette: A. Pete Seeger - Side A, Sax Quartet - Side B, undated (Box 98)
      - Cassette: BCS/Sibelius II, 2000 (Box 99)
      - Cassette: Big Orch and Special Materials, 1981 (Box 99)
      - Cassette: "Blue and Grey" Demo, 1982 (Box 99)
      - Cassette: Congresso Internacional de Musica de Cine - Meeting with the Press (side A), Conference (Side B), 1992 (Box 99)
      - Cassette: Country Excerpts, undated (Box 100)
      - Cassette: Country Sensation, undated (Box 100)
      - Cassette: "Dino" - "Homecoming", undated (Box 100)
      - Cassette: "Dino" - Side A, "Shotgun Slade" - Side B, 1957-1961 (Box 98)
      - Cassette: "The Egg" Complete Score and "Timbuktu" (Gerald Fried), 1959 (Box 101)
      - Cassette: Excerpt Master, October 1983 (Box 100)
      - Cassette: Excerpts of the T.V., Music by Gerald Fried, undated (Box 100)
      - Cassette: Excerpts with Electronics - "Mystic Warrior", "Entam?", "Killer in the Family", 1983-1984 (Box 99)
      - Cassette: "A Fistful of Soundtracks" - K2SC FM Santa Cruz, CA, July 24, 1999 (Box 100)
      - Cassette: Gerald Fried - I and II "Cry-Baby Killer", Machine Gun Kelly", "I, Mobster", "Cast a Long Shadow", undated (Box 100)
      - Cassette: Gerald Fried - "I, Mobster", "Cast a Long Shadow", 1958-1959 (Box 99)
      - Cassette: Gerald Fried - "Machine Gun Kelly", "Cry-Baby Killer", 1958 (Box 99)
      - Cassettes: Gerald Fried, Main Titles, undated (Box 99)
      - Cassette: Gerald Fried - "Return of Dracula" (Side A), "One Potato, Two Potato" (Side B), 1958-1964 (Box 100)
      - Cassette: Gerald Fried - "Take Me to Morning", "California Trail", 1976 (Box 100)
      - Cassette: "Gift of Time" and "Blind Tom", undated (Digital, ahcdm_02883_313-314)
      - Cassette: "The Great Teenage Robbery", "I Bury the Living" (Gerald Fried), undated (Box 99)
      - Cassette: Hitchcock Excerpts, undated (Box 100)
      - Cassette: "Italic Sketches", "Wagon Train" (Gerald Fried), undated (Box 100)
      - Cassette: "It's About Time", "Caligari", undated (Box 100)
      - Cassette: "The Killing", Unknown Score, "Love me a While" (Gerald Fried), 1956 (Box 99)
      - Cassette: Kubrick, undated (Box 100)
      - Cassette: "The Lost Missile", "Trooper Hook", "Dracula", "I Bury the Living", undated (Box 101)
      - Cassette: "Machine Gun Kelly", "Cry-Baby Killer" (Gerald Fried), 1958 (Box 100)
      - Cassette: Main Titles - Master, 1982 (Box 100)
      - Cassette: Masters - "I, Mobster", "Cast a Long Shadow", 1959 (Box 100)
      - Cassette: The Music of Gerald Fried - "Return of Dracula", "Cast a Long Shadow" (suite), "I Bury the Living", "One Potato, Two Potato", 1958-1964 (Box 99)
      - Cassette: Music by Gerald Fried - "Vampire", "Terror in a Texas Town", "Texas", "Bayou", "Criterion MX", "Dracula" Source Cues, undated (Box 100)
      - Cassette: "Mysteryoso", undated (Box 100)
      - Cassette: "The Princess in the Tower", "Les the Least", undated (Box 99)
      - Cassette: Romantic (Side A), Comedy (Side B), 1986 (Box 99)
      - Cassette: "Scary Cruise", undated (Box 100)
      - Cassette: Screen Archives - Gerald Fried "Cast a Long Shadow", "Cry Baby Killer", October 19, 1994 (Box 99)
      - Cassette: Screen Archives - Gerald Fried, Transfers, undated (Box 100)
      - Cassette: "Son-Rise", "Gauguin the Savage", 1979-1980 (Box 100)
      - Cassette: "Sounds of the Night" Demo, 1957-1962 (Box 100)
      - Cassettes: UCLA Sessions, undated (Box 100)
      - Cassette: Unidentified, undated (Box 100)
      - Cassette: "Victims" Backup - "Son-Rise - Enchanted Years", "One Potato, Two Potato", undated (Box 46)
      - CD: "20 Ways"/"Psyche Ascending" Master, 2012-2013 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_308)
      - CD: Edward L. Alperson - "The Restless Breed", 1957 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_114)
      - CD: "The Bell Jar", 2. "Moviola", 3. "Medgar Evers", undated (Digital, ahcdm_02883_013)
      - CD: "The Concert Works", Master, undated (Digital, ahcdm_02883_325)
      - CD: "The Egg", 1962 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_338)
      - CD: Gerald Fried Compilation - "The Princess Tower", "The Treasure", "Les the Least", "Deputy Seraph", undated (Digital, ahcdm_02883_181-183)
      - CD: "Gerald Fried: The Concert Works", undated (Digital, ahcdm_02883_243)
      - CD: "The Killing" and "The Deputy Seraph", 1956-1959 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_115)
      - CD: "Math-net" and "Old MacDonald", 1985 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_113)
      - CD: Phone Conversation Between David Fuller and Gerald Fried, undated (Digital, ahcdm_02883_175)
      - CD: "Terror in a Texas Town" Masters - "Riverboat", "Trooper Hook", "Lost Missile", 1958 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_185-188)
      - CD: Various from Assorted Small Reels, undated (Digital, ahcdm_02883_012)
      - CDs: Ben Casey/ Fried Demo - ("Six Impossible Things", "Dolphins", "Albatross", "Identified", Master without Slates, Sequenced) ("The White Ones are Dolphins - Master with out Slates) ("He Thought He Saw an Albatross" - Master with Slates), undated (Digital, ahcdm_02883_276-284)
      - CDs: "Breakin' Up is Hard to Do" Parts 1-2 - Isolated Proto, "Italic Sketches", 1975 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_138-140)
      - CDs: "Great Teenage Robbery" Revised, Master with Slates, Unidentified, undated (Digital, ahcdm_02883_265-267)
      - CDs: "The Immigrants" parts 1-2 - "The Spell", Master with Slates, 1978 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_194-196, 252-255)
      - CDs: "Whatever Happened to Aunt Alice" Demos, Masters with Slates, "The Killing of Sister George", 1968-1969 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_064-069)
      - CDs and Reel-to-Reels: Assorted Reels, undated (Digital, ahcdm_02883_070-071)
      - CD and Reel-to-Reel: "National Geographic: National Parks" Master, Embassy Reel, undated (Box 103 and Digital, ahcdm_02883_203-204)
      - CD and Reel-to-Reels: "Roadblock" and "Hostage" Unaired TV pilots, Reels 1-2, 1959-1961 (Box 98 and Digital, ahcdm_02883_036)
      - DVD: "Morningtime Train", April 3, 2009 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_292)
      - Reel-to-Reel: Excerpts Master - "Casablanca", "Birds Do It, Bees Do It", "Vigilante Force", "The Immigrants", "The Bell Jar", "Moviola: The Silent Lovers", "For Us the Living: The Medgar Ever Story", 1974-1983 (Box 98)
      - Reel-to-Reel: Fried - "The Man from U.N.C.L.E." ("Alexander the Greater Affair"), "The Killing", "The Cabinet of Caligari", "The Two Five", 1962-1968 (Box 103)
      - Reel-to-Reel: "The Killing of Sister George" - "Gateways", 1968 (Box 98)
    - Visions and Values at Skirball Cultural Center/ Children's Discovery Center
      - Score, 1 of 4, 1997 (Box 23)
      - Score, 2 of 4, 1997 (Box 23)
      - Score, 3 of 4, 1997 (Box 23)
      - Score, 4 of 4, 1997 (Box 23)
      - Score, Recorded by Israel Philharmonic, undated (Box 24)
    - Wesson Oil Commercial
      - Score, undated (Box 24)
    - Western Revised - Nick, Cassette, undated (Box 100)
  - Sub-series 5. Movies
    - 20 Ways
      - Score, 2012 (Box 25)
    - The Baby
      - CDs: Sequenced Cue Master, Isolated Cue Master, Master with Slates, 1973 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_234-237)
      - Cue Sheet, March 28, 1972 (Box 25)
    - Bayou
      - CDs: Master with Slates, Proto, Disc 1-2, 1957 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_332-336)
      - Cinematic Photographs, Black & White, 1957 (Box 106)
      - Cinematic Photographs, Color, 1957 (Box 106)
      - Score, undated (Box 25)
    - The Bell Jar
      - Cassette: KFAC, 1983 (Box 100)
      - 2 Reel-to-Reels and CDs: Masters with Slates, Isolated Proto, Broadcast KFAC, 1979 (Box 102 and Digital, ahcdm_02883_151-153)
      - Score, 1 of 2, undated (Box 25)
      - Score, 2 of 2, undated (Box 25)
      - Suite Score, Parts and Notes, 1998, undated (Box 26)
    - Blind Tom: The Story of Thomas Bethune
      - Cassette: "Genius" G.F. on English Horn, 1966-1987 (Box 99)
      - Score, undated (Box 26)
    - Blood Money
      - Score, undated (Box 26)
    - The Cabinet of Caligari
      - 2 Cassettes, 1962 (Box 100)
      - 3 CDs and 5 Reel-to-Reels, 1962 (Box 99 and Digital, ahcdm_02883_037-039)
      - Score, 1 of 2, undated (Box 26)
      - Score, 2 of 2, undated (Box 26)
    - Cast a Long Shadow
      - Cassette (Gerald Fried), 1959 (Box 99)
      - CDs, 1959 (Digital, ahcdm_02883_141-142)